myfwc.com 2003-06-03

# Privacy Policy

INSURANCENETCENTER PRIVACY POLICY

 **InsuranceNetCenter is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers' personal information.   To better protect the privacy of our customers, we provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online information collection practices and the choices our customers can make about the way their personal information is used at this site.  **

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

 ** _Personally Identifiable Information_  
When you request a quote for an insurance policy, we collect certain personally identifiable information to create your insurance profile, which we share with our participating insurance carriers and agents in order to generate quotes.  The type of personally identifiable information we collect may include your name, address, date of birth, and e-mail address.**

 ** _Personally Identifiable Health Information_   
When you request a quote for a certain policies such as life or health insurance policy, we may collect personal health information, which we share with our participating life or health insurance carriers and agents in order to generate quotes for you.  The type of health information we collect may include height, weight, pre-existing health conditions, whether or not you use tobacco products, etc.**

 ** _Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
_ We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 2000, XP, or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink, etc.).  We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site.  We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products or services.**

 **  
WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION**

 ** _Information We Share Generally_  
Personally identifiable information and personal health information is provided to our participating insurance carriers and agents to generate custom insurance quotes.  Although we do not control the privacy practices of the companies with which we share information, we do require these companies to use the information that we share with them only for the purpose for which the information was provided and in accordance with applicable laws.  Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell our customer lists to others.  **

**_We Do Not Share Health Information_  
Except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy (i.e., for the purpose of generating quotes, and only if required pursuant to legal process and corporate restructuring, as discussed below), it is our policy not to share your personal health information with any third party for any purpose.**

 ** _Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information_  
Unless you opt out as indicated below, we may share certain personally identifiable information with firms that we hire or with which we partner to market certain products or services we think may be of interest to our customers. **

**  
LEGAL PROCESS AND CORPORATE RESTRUCTURING**

 **We may disclose customer information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena, or a law enforcement agency's request.   In addition, in the event that all or substantially all of InsuranceNetCenter's stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, InsuranceNetCenter may transfer such information to the acquiring entity.  **

**  
CHOICES/OPT-OUT**

 **As stated above, we may share the information you provide us (but not personal health information) with firms that we hire or with which we partner in order to market certain products or services we think may be of interest to our customers.   Should you prefer that we not share the information you provide us in this manner, just let us know by sending us an e-mail.**

 **  
COOKIES**

 **InsuranceNetCenter uses "cookies" to enhance users experience with our site.   Cookies are text files we place in a user's computer's browsers to store your preferences.  We use cookies to understand site usage, to personalize users' experience, and to improve the content and offerings on our site.  For example, we may use cookies to personalize users' experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site) and save your password in password-protected areas.  We cannot use our cookies to determine any personally identifiable information about users.**

 **  
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY OTHERS**

 **Our site may contain  resources to other websites whose information practices may be different than ours. Users should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.  **

**SECURITY**

 **We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent against unauthorized access to information that we collect online.   In addition, we use encryption technologies when transferring and receiving certain sensitive information exchanged with our site.  **

**  
REVIEWING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**

 **If you would like to review the personally identifiable information and heath information we have collected about you, you may do so by sending us an e-mail request.**

 **  
CONTACT US**

 **If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on InsuranceNetCenter's privacy practices, please e-mail us.**

 **                                                           [info@insurancenetcenter.com  
](mailto:info@insurancenetcenter.com)  
**
